and I'm firmly of the view as well
that kind of like talking about
things in the way that I'm doing now
so kind of like not in a matter-of-fact
way in a more
theatrical way
maybe hiring a venue and having nobody
in it is a bit of a weird thing to
do but that's the way it's worked
out and then I've got a last one here
which is
stay in the pool
and this is from a video I saw today
I've been posting a lot of videos
of like little snippets of this thing
that I've just done online today
and so I think that's why you know
kind of serendipitously because it's
not serendipity it's the Facebook
algorithm I saw this thing today by
column Tobin I'm always a bit nervous
about pronouncing Irish names but
he was saying that kind of writing
is a bit like he also swims and he
says when he's swimming he's kind of
sometimes he's sitting in the pool
thinking on my back and kind of
like, you know, I'm tired today. I
should get out of the pool and I
shouldn't swim. And he basically said,
like, the whole business of writing
is staying in the pool, staying in
the pool, doing the swimming.
And that's kind of obviously what I
completely failed to do when I kind
of wrote my 20,000 words. I've now
got a 35,000 word mystery story.
And I need to stay in the pool. I
need to kind of, and not just paddle
around in the shallow end. I need
to kind of like, you know, really,
really kind of get on with it. And
I think that's a brilliant way of
ending.